{
    "subject": "resource/A_Lesson_Before_Dying_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/distributor",
    "object": "resource/HBO",
    "human_readable": "The distributor of A Lesson Before Dying (film) is HBO.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8911639451980591,
            "question": "Who distributed the film 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8651682138442993,
            "question": "What is the name of the film distributor associated with 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273671865463257,
            "question": "Which company was responsible for distributing the movie 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7736966609954834,
            "question": "Is 'A Lesson Before Dying' a critically acclaimed film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7023050785064697,
            "question": "What company released the film adaptation of 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6611009240150452,
            "question": "What other movies has HBO distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557585000991821,
            "question": "HBO is known for distributing which type of content?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4787577688694,
            "question": "Has HBO won any awards for distributing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2939873933792114,
            "question": "Besides films, what other types of programming does HBO offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.224352166056633,
            "question": "What are some popular HBO series?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The distributor of A Lesson Before Dying (film) is HBO.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6055_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides films, what other types of programming does HBO offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6055_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has HBO won any awards for distributing films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6055_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=HBO is known for distributing which type of content?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6055_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6055_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about \"A Lesson Before Dying\" being an HBO film, which supports the statement that HBO was its distributor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}